Jim Hazlewood

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CONTACT



(416) 799-7247

linkedin.com/in/jim-h-1000

github.com/CerealJim

https://jim-hazlewood.com/

SKILLS

HTML5 | CSS3 | Sass

JavaScript (ES6+) | ¡Query

React | Firebase | RESTful APIs

Git & Git Hub | Responsive Design

Accessibility | Peer Programming

Code Review | Mustache.js

EDUCATION



Juno College of Technology

Web Development Immersive Bootcamp

Aug 2021 - Oct 2021

Accelerated JavaScript Course

Aug 2021

Web Development Course

Apr 2021 - June 2021



CMA, CPA 2014

Chartered Professional Accountants of Ontario 2014

2011-2014



University of Guelph

Bachelor of Commerce, Accounting 2007-2011

PROFILE

I am a front-end developer with a passion for building accessible, responsive and engaging websites with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React. My work experience as a Web Developer I, has contributed to a heightened level of attention to detail, an ability to work under tight deadlines and to contribute in a team environment while learning and developing best front end practices.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer I

Q4 Inc.

Jan 2022 - Present

- Build accessible and fully responsive investor relation websites for various clients using digital designs and utilizing Q4's Content Management system to customize and build upon website templates. Techologies include HTML5, CSS3, Sass, jQuery.
- Troubleshoot and resolve customer support tickets (Salesforce) and site bugs (BugHerd) through root cause analysis and problem-solving
- Collaborate with appropriate business partners using agile practices (Asana/Jira/Slack) to complete projects in a timely, and adaptive manner.

Senior Financial Analyst

Kellogg Canada Inc.

Jan 2018 - Aug 2021

• Partnered with the Supply Chain and Operations team to provide financial analysis and support on Canada-led cost savings and margin improvement projects.

PROJECTS

Taskify

[LIVE] [REPO]

CSS, REACT, FIREBASE

Created an interactive one-page application that allows the user to add, modify, remove or defer tasks. Using Firebase, data is stored and changed.

Digital Cinephile

[LIVE] [REPO]

SCSS, HTML, JAVASCRIPT, API, PAIR PROGRAMMING

Leveraged MovieDB API to create an app that generates movie and TV recommendations while incorporating JavaScript and error handling.

Box Office Boffo

CSS, REACT, Firebase, API, TEAM PROGRAMMING

App that allows a user to log and rank what movies they think made the most from any year, save those lists and visit them later for comparison.